<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Code &amp; Technics</title><link>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/authors/xavier-camier/</link><description>Recent content on Code &amp; Technics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Xavier Camier; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/authors/xavier-camier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customization of an Hugo Theme</title><link>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/cutomize-theme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/cutomize-theme/</guid><description>I was quite happy of how the Hugo Theme I use look like but I wanted to tailor it a bit so that it aligns more with what I had in mind when starting building that blog. For basic things it is not very difficult. Let&amp;rsquo;s perform two basic examples:
On the front page I want to have the possibility to set a custom description of the post On an article, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to have the number of words count Basics It is not a good idea to edit directly a theme.</description></item><item><title>What I've installed on Ubuntu</title><link>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/what-on-ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 13:30:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/what-on-ubuntu/</guid><description>That page will be updated each time extra needs will be identified.
I want the machine to be a dev machine .net core 3.1 VSCode VSCode extentions (see other post) ### I want to communicate with my office
MS Teams I want to use that machine to edit that blog git brew Hugo Gimp ### I want to have to possibility to play some video on that big iMac screen</description></item><item><title>Vscode Dev Environment</title><link>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/vscode-dev-environment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 13:00:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/vscode-dev-environment/</guid><description>VS Code Extensions not related to a language Extension name Author Usage Material icon Theme publisher Philipp Kief Material Design Icons for Visual Studio Code Path Intellisense Christian Kohler VS Code plugin that autocompletes filenames VS Code Extensions for C# Extension name Author Usage C# for Visual Studio Code Microsoft Syntax highlighting C# Extensions JosKreativ Class creation via contextual menu Nuget Package Manager jmrog Adding/Removing nugget packages VS Code Extensions for Angular Extension name Author Usage Angular Snipets Microsoft Quickly scffold angular file templates Angular Files JosKreativ Quickly scffold angular file templates Angular Languages Angular Service Editor Service for Angular Templates Angular2-switcher infinity1207 Easily navigate to component&amp;rsquo;s files Auto Rename Tag Jun Han Auto rename paired HTML/XML tags Bracket Pair Colorizer 2 CoenraadS A customizable extension for colorizing brackets Debugger for Chrome Microsoft Debug your js code in the chrome browser Prettier Code Formatter Esben Petersen plugin for prettier TSLint Microsoft TSLint support for VS Code</description></item><item><title>Installation of Ubuntu in dual boot with El Capitan</title><link>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/ubuntu-imac-dual-boot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/ubuntu-imac-dual-boot/</guid><description>I bought my 24&amp;rsquo; iMac in March 2009. The latest OSX Version it can support is El Capitan. Althought it is still a very capable machine with its 8 Gb of RAM and its new SSD, the lack of OSX update makes its support of new iCloud features more and more limited. And I can&amp;rsquo;t convert it to a dev machine as the last version of .net core it supports is 2.</description></item><item><title>How This Site Is Built</title><link>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/how-this-site-is-built/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 16:38:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://xcamier.github.io/devExplorerBlog/posts/how-this-site-is-built/</guid><description>Goal: to explain how this site is built To build this web site I use Hugo. Hugo is a static site generator built in go. It is free, easy to understand and highly configurable. In addition to the egine you can download templates to have quickly a look&amp;rsquo;n feel that suits your need. The posts are written in markdown which is very handy to perform quick formatting.
As all the content is text based, it is easy to manage versions, to collaborate and to transfer the site from one machine to another.</description></item></channel></rss>